Hubungi

amidrakhman@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amidrakhman (LinkedIn)

Keahlian Teratas

Pentaho

PostgreSQL

Extract, Transform, Load (ETL)

Certifications

Data Wrangling Python

Fundamental SQL Using FUNCTION and GROUP BY

Google Sertifikat Analisis Data

Data Manipulation with Pandas - Part 2

Data Engineer Challenge with SQL

Amid Rakhman

Junior Data Engineer at Akuntplus.id | Data Enthusiast | Certified Google Data Analytics

Jawa Barat, Indonesia

Ringkasan

I am a fresh graduate with a Bachelor's Degree of Informatics Engineering. Have a career interest in the data field, including Data Engineer, Data Analysts and Data Scientists. I understand python and SQL programming languages for professional data. Internship experience at PT Central AI as Internship Data Scientist.

Pengalaman

Akuntplus Junior Data Engineer November 2022 - Present (7 bulan) Jakarta, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

Central AI (PT Central Artificial Intelligence) Internship Data Scientist Maret 2022 - Juli 2022 (5 bulan)

Indonesia

Implementation Named Entity Recognition Indonesian Language in Chatbot

PT. Roda Prima Lancar Production Operator Juli 2020 - Juni 2022 (2 tahun) Karawang, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

PT Yamaha Indonesia Motor Mfg Production Operator Februari 2018 - Februari 2020 (2 tahun 1 bulan) Karawang, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

PT Toyota Motor Manufacturing Indonesia Production Operator November 2015 - November 2017 (2 tahun 1 bulan) Karawang, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

Pendidikan

Universitas Buana Perjuangan Karawang S1, Informatics Engineering · (September 2018 - Agustus 2022)